To Whom It May Concern:

My name is Ned Nguyen and I am applying for the IT Technician position at Z Networks. In my extensive set of skills, I am thrilled for this opportunity to present myself as a reliable, potential candidate.

To start off, I recently obtained my computer programming certification in addition to having a strong background in Information Technology. I believe having an IT background & computer programming can be an additional benefit to your company.

Not only have I been learning new computer languages in my spare time, but I have also been teaching myself Machine Learning to develop side projects. I have had the pleasure of being a developer for the past two years and would like to use my innovative skills and knowledge to successfully provide your company with solutions across a wide range of software platforms.

With that being said, I like an environment that challenges me with projects requiring me to work outside my comfort zone. I enjoy working closely with a team, and I have had work in cold/dark cave with minimal contacts with humans. I am an autodidact and a quick learner. I can manage well under pressure; therefore, you can always rely on me to keep up with the pace. I have strong communication and team work skills which allows me to work and interact well with others. My future co-workers can always depend on me. In short, I can guarantee you that I will always be on time and accomplish any given tasks. I am willing to take on extra responsibilities and work overtime.

Since I have IT experience and I need to be familiar about your company's task, I am open to salary offered.

Attached is a copy of my resume that details my job duties and education history. I can be reached via email at nmdcnn@gmail or (657) 200-5949 if you have any questions. Please feel free to visit my personal portfolio at <u>nedd.dev</u> for my portfolio. I appreciate and thank you for your time and consideration.

Sincerely, Ned Nguyen

Enclosures: Resume

Visit *nedd.dev* for my portfolio

Ned Nguyen

Orange County, CA

nmdcnn@gmail.com | (657) 200-5949 PORTFOLIO www.nedd.dev

EDUCATION

Orange Coast College *08/2017 – 05/2019*

Computer Programming

Cal State University, Fullerton 08/2011 - 05/2015 Mathematics

Bolsa Grande High School 09/2007 – 05/2011 Computer Repair & General Education

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

Self-employed

05/2017 - Present

- Develop and optimizing the websites and applications with HTML,
 CSS, PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, ReactJS
- Quickly learned JavaScript and Regex in less than a month
- Create custom web pages from themes
- Perform validation of completed sites including the debugging and testing of code
- Create mobile friendly site
- Build websites from start to finish- including all design, graphics, and programming

Providence Partner

Contractor of Public Consulting Group

12/2016 - 05/2017

- Handled supported tickets with software and hardware vendors, evaluated, determined root cause, collaborated with internal and external technical support to ensure 100% problem resolution.
- Perform daily windows imaging (Average of 30 laptops per day)
- Remotely installed drivers and managed client's antivirus/malware software

Kel-Tek Networking Company

Information Systems Analyst

01/2015 - 08/2016

- Diagnosed successfully and resolved hardware and software issues on user workstation
- Installed and maintained hardware and software components on computer stations and IT equipment
- Configured and tuned networking equipment and overall computer network, both ethernet and Wi-Fi successfully

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Hardware

Assembly, Maintenance, Peripherals, Printers, Drivers, Troubleshoot

Software

Installation, Debugging, Microsoft Office, Adobe Photoshop, Git/GitHub, Android Studio

Operating Systems

Windows, macOS, Linux, Android, iOS

Networks

Configuration, Routers, TCP/IP Socket Programming, Lan Technology

Security

Virus Protection, Maintenance, Disaster Recovery

Programming Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, SQL, R, C++, Java

GENERAL SKILLS

Attention to Details

Problem Solving

Teamwork

Communication

INTERESTS

- Artificial Intelligence
- Computer Build & Repair
- Photography
- Hiking